<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days of Wellness</string>
    <string name="tip1_title">Drink a glass of water first thing in the morning</string>
    <string name="tip1_desc">Start your day by hydrating your body to boost metabolism and flush out toxins.</string>
    <string name="tip2_title">Take the stairs</string>
    <string name="tip2_desc">Use stairs instead of elevators to incorporate more physical activity into your daily routine.</string>
    <string name="tip3_title">Make half your plate veggies</string>
    <string name="tip3_desc">Increase your intake of vitamins, minerals, and fiber by filling half your plate with vegetables.</string>
    <string name="tip4_title">Get a fitness tracker and track your steps</string>
    <string name="tip4_desc">Using a fitness tracker helps you stay motivated and ensure you get enough daily movement.</string>
    <string name="tip5_title">Switch to non-toxic household cleaning products</string>
    <string name="tip5_desc">Reduce your exposure to harmful chemicals by using eco-friendly and natural cleaning products.</string>
    <string name="tip6_title">Use non-toxic skincare and personal care products</string>
    <string name="tip6_desc">Protect your skin by choosing products free from harmful chemicals and artificial ingredients.</string>
    <string name="tip7_title">Take a probiotic daily</string>
    <string name="tip7_desc">Support your gut health and digestion by consuming probiotics regularly.</string>
    <string name="tip8_title">Eat real food</string>
    <string name="tip8_desc">Focus on whole, unprocessed foods for better overall health and nutrition.</string>
    <string name="tip9_title">Stand up every 30 minutes while working</string>
    <string name="tip9_desc">Avoid prolonged sitting by standing up and stretching every 30 minutes to improve circulation.</string>
    <string name="tip10_title">Get sunlight every day</string>
    <string name="tip10_desc">Exposure to natural sunlight helps boost vitamin D levels and improve mood.</string>
    <string name="tip11_title">Fill your home with houseplants</string>
    <string name="tip11_desc">Houseplants improve air quality and create a more relaxing environment.</string>
    <string name="tip12_title">Sweat each day</string>
    <string name="tip12_desc">Engage in physical activities that make you sweat to detoxify your body.</string>
    <string name="tip13_title">Have a daily green smoothie</string>
    <string name="tip13_desc">Boost your nutrition by drinking a smoothie filled with greens and healthy ingredients.</string>
    <string name="tip14_title">Go to bed earlier</string>
    <string name="tip14_desc">Prioritize sleep by going to bed early for better energy and overall health.</string>
    <string name="tip15_title">Plan your meals</string>
    <string name="tip15_desc">Meal planning helps you eat healthier and save time during the week.</string>
    <string name="tip16_title">Find a fitness buddy</string>
    <string name="tip16_desc">Stay motivated and accountable by working out with a friend.</string>
    <string name="tip17_title">Make time for self-care</string>
    <string name="tip17_desc">Prioritize activities that relax and recharge you, such as reading or meditation.</string>
    <string name="tip18_title">Put your phone away before bed</string>
    <string name="tip18_desc">Avoid blue light exposure before sleep to improve sleep quality.</string>
    <string name="tip19_title">Take a prebiotic daily</string>
    <string name="tip19_desc">Prebiotics help nourish the good bacteria in your gut, improving digestion.</string>
    <string name="tip20_title">Practice deep breathing</string>
    <string name="tip20_desc">Deep breathing helps reduce stress and promotes relaxation.</string>
    <string name="tip21_title">Eat the rainbow</string>
    <string name="tip21_desc">Consume a variety of colorful fruits and vegetables for a balanced diet.</string>
    <string name="tip22_title">Chew your food thoroughly</string>
    <string name="tip22_desc">Proper chewing aids digestion and helps your body absorb nutrients more effectively.</string>
    <string name="tip23_title">Practice gratitude</string>
    <string name="tip23_desc">Take time each day to reflect on things you\'re grateful for to boost happiness.</string>
    <string name="tip24_title">Stop eating before you\'re full</string>
    <string name="tip24_desc">Eat mindfully and stop before feeling completely full to avoid overeating.</string>
    <string name="tip25_title">Find a creative outlet</string>
    <string name="tip25_desc">Engage in creative activities like painting, writing, or playing music to reduce stress.</string>
    <string name="tip26_title">Make time to stretch</string>
    <string name="tip26_desc">Stretching improves flexibility and helps prevent injuries.</string>
    <string name="tip27_title">Spend time in nature</string>
    <string name="tip27_desc">Being in nature can reduce stress, improve mood, and boost overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="tip28_title">Read ingredient labels</string>
    <string name="tip28_desc">Check labels to make informed choices about the food and products you consume.</string>
    <string name="tip29_title">Practice good dental hygiene</string>
    <string name="tip29_desc">Brush and floss daily to maintain healthy teeth and gums.</string>
    <string name="tip30_title">Laugh often</string>
    <string name="tip30_desc">Laughter reduces stress and improves overall happiness.</string>
    <string name="tip31_title">Get a houseplant</string>
    <string name="tip31_desc">Having plants in your home can purify the air and create a calming environment.</string>


</resources>